mymagicfundas.com 2017-07-28

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Mymagicfundas collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the http://www.mymagicfundas.com blog. This privacy policy applies to the blog and all products and services offered by Mymagicfundas.

## Personal Identification Information

I (Nirmala) may collect personal identification information from users/readers in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when they visit my site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources that I make available on my blog. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. They may, however, visit my blog anonymously. I’m collecting personal identification information from my visitors only if they voluntarily submit such information to me. They can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain blog related activities.

## Non-personal Identification Information

I may collect non-personal identification information about the blog visitors whenever they interact with my blog. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about the visitors means of connection to my blog, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web Browser Cookies

My blog may use “cookies” to enhance the user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the blog may not function properly.

### How I Use Collected Information?

Mymagicfundas may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve my blog

I may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

– To send periodic emails

I may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### How I Protect User’s Information?

I adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of the user’s personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

My blog is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for my blog readers. 

### Sharing Personal Information

I do not sell, trade, or rent my users personal identification information to others. I may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about my readers or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to them. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to my blog and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about my blog readers, such as their name, email address, physical address, etc. They may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, I never collect or maintain information at my blog from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age 13.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

Mymagicfundas has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When I do, I will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. I encourage my readers to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how I’m are helping to protect the personal information that I collect. They should acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Acceptance

By using my blog, my readers signify their acceptance of this policy. If they do not agree to this policy, they may avoid my blog to visit. Their continued use of my blog following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed their acceptance of those changes.

#### Contact Me

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices/dealings with this blog, Please contact me through the **[contact form](http://www.mymagicfundas.com/contact-us/)**  or nirmala@mymagicfundas.com

This document was last updated on 14th August, 2015.

Privacy policy created by http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com
